#### Contact

+61410980370 (Mobile) pramukam@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pramukaperera-9414b2a6 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript

HTML5

css

## Languages

English (Full Professional)
Sinhalese (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Certificate in Web Designing Certificate in Computerized accounting

# Pramuka Perera

Junior Web Developer with financial accounting skills Narre Warren

## Summary

I am a junior web developer coming from a financial accounting background. I have experience in the hospitality industry as an Income Auditor, for more than four years. I strongly believe that accountants should integrate their accounting skills with coding skills to embrace future technological changes.

# Experience

Anantara Hotels, Resorts and Spas 2 years 7 months

Income Audit Supervisor June 2016 - March 2018 (1 year 10 months) Salalah, Oman

Pre-opening / Post opening

- To balance and audit all Front office postings and settlements.
- To verify that all departments have posted all their revenues.
- To verify, monitor, and review all hotel reports and night audit reports.
- To be responsible for month-end deadlines and schedules.
- To reply to the Credit Card Charge Backs from Network International and American express and respond to all credit card inquiries
- To reconcile Credit Card commissions on a daily basis
- To reconcile the food and beverage point of sale system, for each outlet, to the PMS system and where necessary, record and adjust entries.
- To monitor front office rebates. Review and balance rebates, paid-outs, miscellaneous charges and staff charges to the property management system and ensure that each account is properly authorized and has relevant explanations.
- To review F&B voids to verify authorization and adequate back-up information.
- To prepare "Daily Operational Package" that is routed to GM, Controller, F&B Director, & Revenue Director.
- To follow-up and report any notes raised by any signatories.

- To assist with month-end closing and subsequent analysis of bank accounts and other balance sheet accounts as directed by the accountant.
- To prepare month end income journal entries, according to the policy and using standard templates
- To assist the General Cashier in performing surprise float counts.
- To report any problems or discrepancies to the Accountant on a daily basis.
- To replace Receivable Supervisor and General cashier in his/her absence
- To complete various other accounting tasks and duties as required by accounting management

Income Auditor September 2015 - June 2016 (10 months) Tangalle

Income Auditor (Pre-Opening/Post-Opening Team Member)

AVANI Hotels and Resorts
Accounting Assistant
June 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 4 months)
AVANI Kalutara

General accounts receivable functions

- Prepare and submit customer invoices
- Code, post and receipt payments
- Prepare and coordinate deposit activities
- Perform all necessary account, bank and other reconciliations
- Monitor customer accounts for non-payment and delayed payment

General accounts payable functions

- Check, verify and process invoices
- Prepare payments for signature
- Sort, code and enter accounts payable data
- Analyze discrepancies and unpaid invoices
- Maintain vendor files

#### General support functions

- Verify, update and maintain accounting journals and ledgers and other financial records
- Assist in month end reporting procedures

- Find and use accounting data to resolve accounting problems and discrepancies
- Track and audit petty cash
- Assist with employee expense reports
- Perform filing and general administrative tasks
- Liaise with other departments/customers/vendors

## Education

Holmes Institute, Australia

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Business Administration and Management, General · (2019 - 2020)

Holmes Institute, Australia

Master of Professional Accounting · (2018 - 2020)

The Chartered Institute of Management Accountants
CIMA Advanced Diploma in Management Accounting (CIMA Adv Dip
MA), Management Accounting

Holy Cross College Kalutara

Business/Commerce, General · (1998 - 2011)